ED]
Next Trailer
How are you guys running?
Where are we going?
No way.
Yes, yes, yes.
How are you guys running?
I'm so embarrassed.
It's okay.
I'm...
Me, me, me.
What's the one thing you can't lose?
This is the one thing we can't lose.
You know that hand-push wrestling?
After I beat all the staff members.
I beat all the staff members, and I lost with one shot.
Then, I'm the best, right?
Let's do it.
So, I lost.
And the other thing is, you know, Aya...
The scene where he chases after Aya after she went to the coach.
After she says, "See you later, Kan-chan.
Then we run as fast as we can.
We were running as fast as we could, and we weren't filming anything.
We're not even on camera, but for some reason, Ryu and I...
We were really running.
We were running together.
It was a tie at first.
It was a tie.
And I'm like, "Okay, I'm gonna go for it.
I passed him at the end.
We lost.
We won.
I don't know what I was doing running.
I didn't want to go looking for him. I just wanted to run.
What's the one thing I can't lose?
I'm Go Yoshizumi, the one who never loses.
By the way, I won the ping-pong match.
I lost.
It's amazing... every time we play, he grows in the game.
It's like he's growing up.
How wide are your shoulders and how big is the threat?
I don't know about shoulders.
As for threats, well, I'm new at this.
I was 5'9" before I joined Lamman, and I'm 5'9" now.
How come I didn't gain 6 inches?
I've gained 12 cm in 4 months.
You'll do the same.
How the hell did I gain that much?
What is this?
What do you think about Kamikiku's fashion sense?
I wonder how you feel about this question.
I'm curious... what do you mean?
Do you have any thoughts about it?
Because that's how I feel, isn't it?
But you know what?
Well...
I've been watching Ryu's shtick since Bolzuna.
Well, Ryu...
I like his clothes.
But...
It's more than that.
I'm more conscious of how easy it is.
I'm more conscious of how I get to and from work sites.
That's exactly what I was doing the other day.
the other day, Ryu came in his usual Ma-chan Aggie outfit.
And then...
After that, Jun said, "I'm going shopping with you for a while.
And when Ryu said, "I'm going to go after I change my clothes...
He was so stylish.
That set-up.
Yes, yes, yes... that time.
I thought Ryu was dressed up to the nines. It looked good on him.
You were so cute!
Look, I've been on Twitter.
I was on stage in Shibuya, shaking hands with a god.
I was dressed like a junior high schooler.
Why did you do that? No, it's okay.
It's okay. You're so upset about it.
His middle-school clothes... okay, okay, Ryu, I get it.
You have your own special style. When you go shopping...
If you do it in a different way every day, you'll be really stylish.
I see. Every day you put your best effort into it?
You should choose about 10 outfits and wear them every day.
I see... do you want to do something in your lifetime? Is there a place you want to go?
I want to go there.
Where?
That place in Africa.The African one.
Hey!
The jungle.
What? Not Savannah?
There's a tour like Savannah.
What's a savanna tour?
Like, when you're driving around and there's all these wild animals.
I'd like to see that.
Or something like that. Like crossing the Amazon or the Nile.
I'd like to see statues next to them.
I'd like to see something like that.
I went to Savannah when I was 8.
Tinian.
Oh! You went there. It's a work of art, right?
Yeah, but it was so much fun.
Were there a lot of wild animals?
Yes! Like the shetan.
Lions.
Gachitarra cheetah? I saw a sanctuary cheetah.
I was at that guy's shelter, and I was brushing this thing like this.
You've seen a cheetah in the wild? You ever see a cheetah in the wild? I have.
Oh, my God! Oh, man! What do you want to do, Dereux?
Well, you know, I'd like to see the Northern Lights.
Oh, yeah, that's a good idea. Up in Canada.
Up or down, I guess, relative to the Earth's axis.
Solar wind, right? Yeah.
So it's like a whoosh.
You mean you can see the top? You mean you can see it at the North Pole?
You mean you can see it at the South Pole?
I'd like to see it. At least once.
I'd like to see it at least once.
What was the most impressive thing about today's venue?
Today's venue means he might have been pissed off.
He might have been pissed off.
He might have been.
There was a lot of heat.
It was probably, you know, about 15 degrees hotter than people think they see on TV.
It was hot.
You know, you wrote that your face was shiny, but I was peeling...
This is shiny.
No, you can't do that.
That's shiny.
Everybody was shiny. My armpits were soaked with sweat.
They were sweating like crazy.
But, I don't know, but I was cold at first. I was a little...
Yeah. - Yeah.
I was cold, but it's been a while since I've been on the air.
Isn't it a little scary that your first show in a long time is live?
It's nerve-wracking.
I was a little relieved, but I also felt like I had to be firm.
But slowly, everyone was warming up to me, and I could see the smiles on their faces.
And when I see the smiles on the faces of the audience.
I'm glad I did it.
It's something I've been carrying around.
I'm relieved.
That's what's so great about it.
Seeing your voices and the expressions on your faces was a great source of power for me today.
I'm really grateful for that, and I'm glad I did my best.
I have a question for Mr. C. Did you notice your habit of swaying from side to side while talking on TV?
Did you find yourself swaying again today? I think it's cute.
But I get that a lot from my manager.
I'm often told that by my manager.
Oh, that's why I do it so often in the play.
Hmmm...
I say, "Well, you're right.
So I often tell the director, "Oh, don't shake that.
You follow the camera, don't you?
Yeah.
I noticed something.
I've noticed it when he tells me.
I don't notice it while I'm doing it.
My grandma, when she watches TV.
She always nods her head like this.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I always say, "Hey, you're nodding.
She says, "No, I'm not nodding.
That's how it is.
It's a Ma-chan trait.
It's important.
Mac, we were at the same place at the same time.
Yes, we did.
I was happy about that, too.
But surprisingly...
You and I...
We have a lot of rivalries.
Yes, we do.
There's a lot of rivalry.
Don't you want to do commercials together?
Me and Ryu have been talking about this for a while.
Runman.
We've been saying that we want to do a commercial for the two of us after the week or after Ranman is over.I've been saying all week that I'd love to do a commercial for the two of you after the week or the run man.
I definitely want to do it.
That's... please.
Please do.
There's a lot of that rivalry.
I have something we can be friends with.
We're friends.
I look forward to working with you.
I'll let the two of us fool around together. Please take care of it.
Just now...
It's official.
You know how he said his face is different?
Mantarou the dragon.
Mantaro's face is different when he's in Kochi and when he's in Tokyo.
I told a reporter in an interview that his face is different when he's in Kochi and when he's in Tokyo.
Was it that different?
Not even close.
Seriously?
I went to college alone for 7 weeks.
I went to college alone for seven weeks.
I was kind of surprised.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
I was like, "Wow." As I was looking at her, was she that different?
Wow, no.
I thought, "Wow, he's doing it." No, I heard that.
In a good way. In a good way.
I thought, "Oh, that's not fair.
But when you're in front of me, your face changes again? It's always real.
You know... there was a time when I really understood... the Todai team is really close right now.
Hatano-kun, Fujimaru-kun...
We get along really well.
They talk a lot on the street, and Shibaichi jokes around, but...
But there's a scene where they're together and Takeo comes in.
They have fun together, of course.
But when Jun comes in, he makes me feel safer.
You were saying something about that.
That's what she meant. He's here!
I heard something about that.
You know...
He's a makeup artist called Kun Kun.
He's a makeup artist called Kun-kun.
AKA Kun-kun.
He's doing my makeup, right?
Yes, that's right.
It's been a week since I've been there.
I was talking with Mr. Kamiki.
It's only five days until Junga comes, right?
The next day, he said, "Only 4 more days until Junga comes.
He said he's counting down the days. I thought it was cute.
I'm relieved. - Of course I am.
Of course I'm relieved. I trust him, and of course I'm happy to see him.
I'm having fun, but... there's a difference between reassurance and reassurance.
I do feel secure, but... No.
When the order comes...
I'm glad I'm back to my usual low range.
But I guess Mantaro was like that too. I'm sure he was.
I guess that's what the Showa era is all about.
That's why...
Thank you very much for applying.
Thank you very much.
You're recruiting, aren't you?
Here we go!
Thank you for applying on such short notice.
I'm sorry we had to do it on such short notice.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for all your comments.
Thanks to you, I was able to ask a lot of questions in order.
I can't believe that this is really filmed and put on YouTube.
I can't believe that this is going to be on YouTube.
I don't know that this is going to be on YouTube.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I don't know if it's okay.
But it's like this is how we usually talk.
Yeah, this is what I'm talking about.
It would be nice to share it with everyone.
I want to go on a road trip with you next time.
I want to go.
We'll have some food.
I don't want to show it on youtube.
I don't want to show it on youtube. And we've probably been on a lot of road trips before, but...
I don't think we've ever talked like this before. I've seen old videos of him. He's a little more careful.
Ryu-chan, I'm going to go in there.
Ryu-chan, there was a little more distance, but now that you've seen it, maybe you'll understand.
It's not often I'm this insecure about something.
Let's do a second project during Ranmaru or something.
I'm sure Ryu's busy, but...
I'm sure Ryu's busy, but something like driving, hitting a ball, bowling, and eating dinner is the best we can do.
Let's do it! Let's do it!
Then, please wait for the second project!
And now, from the Ranmaru Tramway in Daichi Prefecture...So here we are, from the Ranmaru Tramway in Daichi Prefecture, Japan.
Take care of yourselves, everyone!
Yay!